(Howard:)...you have to get the head
of the decorating committee too?
(Leonard:)-What are you talking about?
-Look, don't play innocent with me.
(Howard:)I practically invented using
fancy lab equipment to seduce women.
(Leonard:)-Has it ever worked?
-Not so far, but that's not the point.
(Leonard:)Howard, relax.
I am not interested in your girlfriend.
(Howard:)I hope not,
because you don't wanna mess with me.
(Howard:)I'm crazy.
(Leonard:)I believe you.
SHELDON:
Research journal, entry one.
(Sheldon:)I'm about to embark on one of the great
challenges of my scientific career:
(Sheldon:)teaching Penny physics.
(Sheldon:)I'm calling it Project Gorilla.
(Penny(knocking and entering):)-Hey, Sheldon.
-Come in. Take a seat.
(Sheldon:)Subject has arrived.